翻译校对       Mam
日  听      大海
日听校对       Syura
翻译        葉隠
时间轴       鬼 忻奈
压制      娜夏
OP&ED       葉隠
Syura
诸神字幕组
"I love you. You're all I can think about."
好きだ
君のことだけを考えている
"Let's spend the rest of our lives
together, just the two of us."
これからはずっと僕と二人きりで過ごそうよ
"I'm so happy, Miyabi- kun''
"I can't right now..."
I'm so happy, Miyabi- kun.
嬉しいわ　雅君
Miss? The Master has returned home.
お嬢様　旦那様がお帰りになられました
Miss?
お嬢様
蓮華
Renge...
蓮華は本当にゲームが好きだね
Renge, you really do
love those games, huh?
Is that so wrong?
いけない？
No, no,
your father wants you to live
your life free and at ease, Renge,
お父さんは蓮華の思うままに伸び伸びと生きててほしいんだ
however you want to live it.
If there's anything you want to do,
I'll let you do it. I promise.
望むことなら　何でもさせてあげるよ　約束する
Sure.
"France"
How was your business in Japan?
日本でのお仕事はどうでしたの
It should turn out well. Oh, right,
うまくいきそうだよ
そうそう　先週取り引き先のご一家と食事をしてね
last week, I had dinner
in the home of one of my clients.
ほら　これがその時の写真だ
Here. This is a photograph from it.
They had a boy in high school, too.
あちらにも高校生のお子さんがいたよ
Father...
お父様
I am going to marry him!
わたくし　彼と結婚するわ
Please keep that promise you
made to me earlier, Father!
先ほどの約束　必ず守ってくださいね　お父様
H-hey, Renge...
お　おい　蓮華
Just you wait, my prince!
待ってて　わたくしの王子様
Renge!
蓮華　蓮華～
Renge!!
"The Host Club is now open for business"
Tamaki- kun...
環君　環君は何故そんなにお美しいの
Tamaki- kun, why is it that
you are so beautiful?
一秒でも長く　君の目に留まりたいからさ
Because I want to catch your eye,
if only for one second longer.
Why is it that your voice is so mellow?
So that my feelings might reach your heart.
僕の思いが君の心まで届くように
何故そんな濡れた瞳でわたくしを
Why is it that you look at me
with such moist eyes?
みずみずしい君の笑顔が
Because your fresh, young smile
makes the spring in my heart overflow.
僕の心の泉を溢れさせるからさ
- Tamaki- kun...
環君
The two of you would
wear matching kimonos, huh?
やっぱり二人はお揃いの着物なのね
今日のは全員　うちの母がデザインしたやつだよ
The ones that everyone is wearing
today were designed by our mother.
"Beauty"
よかったら　オーダー承ります
If you like, we can take your order.
It was our grandmother
that dressed us, though.
着付けたのは祖母だけどね
And of course, it's my task
to undress you, Kaoru.
もちろん　脱がせるのは俺の役目だよな　馨
Hikaru...
光　恥ずかしいよ　みんなの前で
You're embarrassing me,
in front of the others...
あ～もう　脱がせるんだなんて
- What a tender embrace!
- They're up to their nonsense again.
また馬鹿やってる
あ～ダメ～
Haruhi- kun!
ハルヒ君　着物姿も可愛いのね
You look so cute in a kimono.
You almost look like a girl in it.
まるで女の子みたい
Yeah...
ハルヒ　ご指名だ
Haruhi, you've been requested.
Your clients have pretty well
stabilized lately, haven't they?
最近は接客も大分安定してきたじゃないか
Keep it up.
その調子だ
We're not planning to charge interest
on the original debt you incurred,
本来付くべき借金の利子まで請求する気はないから
so just keep working hard, and pay it off.
頑張って稼いでくれよ
The rental fee for that kimono
is nothing to sneeze at, after all.
その着物のレンタル代だって　馬鹿にならないんだからね
Who is this guy,
the crooked magistrate?
悪代官か　この人は
Kyoya-sama...
鏡夜様
You're just too much, in that kimono.
その着物姿も堪りませんわ
Are there any new photo collections
of the Host Club coming out?
ホスト部の新しい写真集はまだ出ませんの
Unfortunately, nothing
is scheduled at present.
残念ながら　いまのところ予定は
The club makes much of its money...
うちの部はグッズ販売で
...from the sale of
promotional items, right?
ずいぶん稼いでいるんでしょう
そのグッズ自体が弱くてな
The promotional items
themselves are poor.
The photo collections are just
amateur hidden camera shots.
写真集などと言っても　素人が隠し撮りしたものだし
In order to draw even more for the
club's expenses out of the school budget,
学院予算から更に部費を引き出すためにも
もっと優良な商品開発を実現しなくては
we have to start coming up with
some higher-quality products.
この人だからこそ
It's only because of him that this club
can operate without going bankrupt.
この部を破産させずに運営できてるんだな
Haru-chan, Haru-chan...
ハルちゃん　ハルちゃん
I lost one of my sandals.
草履　片っ方なくなった
You were just wearing them
a while ago, weren't you?
さっきまで履いてたじゃないですか
Mitsukuni...
光邦
Takashi...
崇
It was lying over there.
向こうに落ちてた
崇～
Takashi!
素敵
Fantastic!
It is fantastic!
素敵ね
These tearful scenes seem to be spreading.
何か涙ものが流行ってるな
How is it that everyone
can get so weepy so suddenly?
皆何であんなにすぐに泣けるんだろう
Whoops...
"High-grade"
This?
I should let you know,
it's a common practice for a host.
言っとくけど　こんなのホストの常識だから
There isn't a girl around
who won't swoon over moist eyes.
濡れた瞳によろめかない女はいないのさ
That's cheating.
ずるい
Oh, don't be so rigid.
まっ　固いこと言わない
ほら　ハルヒ　これやるから
Here, Haruhi.
This is for you.
I can have this?
くれるの？
How charming!
かわゆいね
Haruhi- kun, you like confections?
ハルヒ君　和菓子好きなの
No, I'm not much for sweets.
いえ　甘い物はあまり
Still, it might be nice as a
memorial offering for my mother.
でも　母の仏前に供えたらいいかなって
How admirable of you!
何て健気なんだ
Such devotion to your mother!
Here, Haruhi, take as many as you like!
そんな親思いのところもいい
さ　ハルヒ　好きなだけ持っておいき
Are those fake tears, too?
その涙も偽物
How can you say that!?
何を言う
My tears are always genuine.
俺の涙はいつだって本物だ
目薬など使わずに泣けるようになってこそ
Being able to cry without using eye drops
is the mark of a true host.
本物のホストだ
どうだ　感心したか
Well? Are you impressed?
Have you fallen for me anew?
惚れ直したかにゃ
Not really.
別に
My overtures just don't seem
to reach you, huh Haruhi?
どうもハルヒには　俺のアピールが届かんな
Perhaps I should alter
my character somewhat.
少しキャラを変えたほうがいいのかにゃ
Huh? We have a brand-new guest.
あれ　お客さん新顔だね
どうしたの　入っておいでよ
What are you waiting for? Come on in.
It isn't any fun to just watch.
見てるだけじゃつまんないよ
- Come on.
- U-um...
Hey, I'm always telling you
to be more courteous
初めてのお客様には
to our first-time guests, aren't I?
もっと丁寧にしろといつも言ってるだろう
Here, don't be afraid, my princess.
さぁ　怖がらないで　お姫様
ようこそ　桜蘭ホスト部へ
Welcome to Ouran Host Club.
N-
N-?
いや　触らないで　この偽者
No! Don't touch me, you phony!
I'm... a phony?
俺が　偽者？
Yes! You're a phony!
そう　偽者よ
I can't believe that you are
the prince figure in this club!
あなたがこの部の王子様的存在だなんて信じられませんわ
The prince character doesn't go
spreading his love around so readily!
王子キャラたるもの　そう安々と愛を振り撒いたりしないもの
How can you be so stupid!? It's almost
like you're a dim-witted narcissist!
どうしてそんなに馬鹿みたいなの
"Stupid"
まるで頭の悪いナルシストじゃない
"Narcissist"
"Incompetent"
Incompetent! Mediocre! The pits!
無能　凡人　最低
"Commoner"
"Disgusting"
Oh, it's a new technique!
新技だ
One-man slow-motion!
一人スローモーション
By any chance, are you...
君は　もしや
鏡夜様
Kyoya-sama!
I've wanted to meet you.
お会いしたかった　わたくしだけの王子様
My own prince.
"Music Room #3"
Fiancée?
許婚
"Music Room #3"
Kyoya- senpai's?
鏡夜先輩の
Yes. My name is Hoshakuji Renge.
はい　宝積寺蓮華と申します
I will be transferring into
1st-Year, Class A tomorrow.
明日から一年A組に転入することになりました
Look, he's mad.
ほら　怒ってるよ
That's because Mommy was
hiding something from Daddy.
お母さんがお父さんに隠し事していたから
"Daddy"
"Mommy"
Whatever. Are you trying to make
this married couple thing stick?
どうでもいいが　その夫婦設定は定着させていくつもりか
It is indeed love at first sight.
まさに一目惚れでございました
The way you were adoring those flowers
by yourself in the back courtyard,
誰にも見向きもされない裏庭の花を一人慈しむそのお姿に
even when no one else was looking...
そして　傷ついた子ネコに優しく差し伸べたその手に
And the way you kindly reached out
to that injured little kitty...
Who are we talking about?
それは誰
Could you have the wrong person?
人違いでは
No! You can't fool these eyes!
いいえ　この目に狂いはありませんわ
He's someone who is kind to everyone,
"Who? Who? Who?"
誰にでも優しく
それでいて決して見返りを求めたりしない人
and yet does not seek to have
anyone take notice of him.
孤独を愛し　だけど本当は寂しがりや
He loves solitude,
but is actually, lonesome.
The one who looks just like
the star of the currently popular
今をときめく恋愛シミュレーションゲーム
love simulation game,
"Uki-doki Memorial,"
"Uki-Doki Memorial"
「うき❤ドキ★メモリアル」の一条雅君にそっくりなあなた
Ichijo Miyabi- kun, and that's you!
Uki?
(Uki - high-spirited)
Doki?
(Doki - heart-pounding)
An otaku!
オタク
She's an otaku!
オタクだ
始めて見た
I've never seen one before!
なるほど　キャラ萌え系か
I see now. You're infatuated
with a character.
萌えキャラに俺を当てはめ
You're projecting the character
infatuation onto me,
going so far as to delude yourself
that we are engaged.
婚約者という妄想にまで及んだと
This Miyabi- kun character
probably wears glasses too, right?
おそらく　雅君というのはメガネキャラなのだろう
Whoa, deluded, you say? Then,
that story about her being your fiancée...
や　妄想って
じゃ　お前の許婚って話は
一度たりとも肯定した覚えはないが
I don't remember ever acknowledging that.
For one thing, I've never
even met her before today.
第一　彼女とは今日が初対面だ
"You could have said so sooner"
According to my information,
調書によりますと
Kyoya-sama, I understand that you
administer everything about this club.
鏡夜様はこの部の一切を管理されておられるとか～
That's right. Kyo-chan is our director.
そうだよ　鏡ちゃん　店長さん
The director? That's perfect!
店長様　ぴったりですわ
I've always dreamed of being the
drawing card for someone's business.
わたくし　お店の看板娘になるのが夢だったんです
We don't need one.
We're a host club, after all.
いらないよ　ホスト部だから
I've made up my mind. I'm going
to be this host club's manager!
決めましたわ
わたくし　このホスト部のマネージャーになります
"She's not listening"
おい　鏡夜
Hey, Kyoya...
She's the daughter of a client
that's important to the Otori family.
彼女は我が鳳家の大切な取引先のご令嬢だ
I ask that you be sure not
to do anything impolite.
くれぐれも失礼のないように頼む
Everyone, it's going to be a pleasure.
"For whatever reason,
it's the birth of a lady manager"
皆さん　よろしくお願いしますね
"The next day"
I thought about it all last night,
昨夜一晩　考えてみたんだが
and having a lady manager
might not be all that bad.
女子マネージャーも　悪くないかもしれない
Why do you say that?
そりゃまたどうして
Don't you see? She has transferred
into the same class as Haruhi.
分からんか
彼女はハルヒと同じクラスに編入されたんだぞ
If the two both become friends as girls,
Haruhi might become more girlish.
女同士の友達ができれば
ハルヒももっと女の子らしくなるかもしれん
The uniquely girlish air
of tenderness about her
女の子特有の柔らかな雰囲気が
could stimulate Haruhi's
own sense of femininity.
ハルヒに女としての自覚を促す
Good grief...
This is a grand-scale project in order
to stir Haruhi up to be more girly!
これはハルヒを　より乙女チックに目覚めさせる
一大プロジェクトなのだ
Only having these two disreputable
twins as close classmates,
クラスメートの仲良しがこんないかがわしい双子だけじゃ
ハルヒのためにならん
is not good for Haruhi.
That's telling us, all right.
言ってくれるね
みなさん
People...
Renge, your Host Club drawing card,
has baked some cookies.
ホスト部看板娘の蓮華が　クッキーを焼いて参りました
Oh... how ladylike! I'm so moved!
お～女の子らしい　感動したぞ～俺は
I didn't bake them for you,
you phony prince.
あんたのために焼いたんじゃないわよ　ニセ王子
"Phony prince"
They're a little bit burnt, but I know
what you're going to say, Kyoya-sama.
すこし焦がしてしまいましたの
でも分かっていますわ　鏡夜様ならなんっておっしゃるか
"Anything you make is going
to be delicious, of course."
君の作った物なら　おいしいに決まってるじゃないか
いや～もう～鏡夜様ったら
Oh, Kyoya-sama...
You're right, these are burnt.
確かに焦げすぎだな
Mitsukuni, stop. They're bad for you.
光邦止せ　体にわるい
こわい こわいよ～
She's scaring me!
They're savory, and not all that bad.
香ばしくて　そんなにわるくないけど
Let me see...
Oh, Haruhi, you have
cookie crumbs on your face.
あれ　ハルヒ　クッキーの粉が付いてるぞ
ひゃ～　あいつら あいつら
Before anyone realized it, they've
become a congenial classmate trio.
いつの間にやら　クラスメートの仲良し三人組だな
あいつら　お母さん　あいつら　お母さん
You know, if you'd just say so,
I could get them off myself.
あのね　言ってくれれば　自分で取るし
And if you wanted one, they're right here.
欲しけりゃこっちにあるんだから
お　お　お　お前のリアクションは間違っています
Y-y-your reaction is all wrong!
This is where you're
supposed to rebuff them,
そこは拒絶すべきところであって
軽く流すところでは
and casually brush them aside!
Please stop sexually harassing me, Senpai.
セクハラはやめてください　先輩
"Rebuff"
Harassing you!? If I'm harassing you,
then they're twice as guilty!
セクハラ？
俺がセクハラならあいつらは凶悪犯だ
お巡りさん～
Aah! Police!
Okay, okay, sir, we're sorry.
はいはい　殿　ごめんってば
Renge-chan, Renge-chan...
蓮華ちゃん　蓮華ちゃん
ミルク　飲む
Want some milk?
それは嫌だな
俺はキングだぞ
Too tepid...
ぬるい
はい　はい　殿
ぬるいですわ
It's all too tepid!
Except for Kyoya-sama, all of your
characters are too lackluster!
鏡夜様以外　総じてキャラがぬるい
All of you hosts are
lacking a "dark" side!
ここのホストはあまりに影が欠如していますわ
Girls are vulnerable to handsome
young men going through trauma!
乙女は美少年のトラウマに弱いもの
If you keep carrying on
in this ridiculous manner,
こんな馬鹿みたいなノリだけでは
飽きられるのも時間の問題
it's only a matter of time
before everyone grows tired of it!
Are you trying to ruin
Kyoya-sama's precious business!?
あなた方は鏡夜様の大事なお店を潰す気ですの
マネージャーとして　今日からキャラ設定を一新します
As manager, starting today, I'm changing
all of your character backgrounds.
Starting with you!
まずあなた
If all you are is cute, inside and out,
then you're the same as a baby.
外見も中身も可愛いだけなら幼児と同じ
As such, you're now
よって　可愛い顔して実は鬼畜
"The cute face, who's actually a thug!"
Morinozuka- senpai, you're the
銛之塚先輩は　幼馴染の子分
"Childhood-friend flunkie!"
The twins will be basketball players,
双子は二人きりの世界に閉じこもるバスケット選手
"Shut up in their own world!"
Haruhi- kun, you're an honor student,
faced with
ハルヒ君は　優等生だけど　激しいいイジメ遭っている
"Intense bullying!"
And Tamaki- san, you are the school idol,
esteemed for your looks,
そして環さん
あなたは外見ばかりを評価され
but actually, you have
an inferiority complex...
実はコンプレックスを抱える学院のアイドル
孤独な王子
"Lonesome Prince!!"
Oh, Kyoya-sama, you're perfect.
鏡夜様は完璧ですわ
いつも慈愛に満ちた　優しいあなたでいてね
You just stay your usual kind,
affectionate self.
I'm honored.
光栄だよ
"The lonesome prince."
Indeed, that is perfect for me!
孤独な王子
確かに　俺にぴったりだ
That's probably the one
she got most wrong.
たぶん　一番間違ってる
Kyoya- senpai...
鏡夜先輩さ
Do something!
どうにかしてよ
But his highness seems up for this.
だが　部長が乗り気だよ
Renge- kun, Renge- kun...
蓮華君　蓮華君
孤独なポーズとは　こんなものだろうか
Is this what a lonesome pose
would look like?
My, that's pretty good, Tamaki- san.
ま～なかなかですわ　環さん
I'm sure it would be even
more effective if it were raining.
雨が降ってると　より効果的ですわ　きっと
まっ　様子を見ようじゃないか
Well, let's just see
how it goes, why don't we?
Something interesting
will come of it, I'll bet.
おもしろいことになるよ　たぶんね
Get a stretcher! Take him
to the infirmary, quick!
担架だ　すぐに医務室に運ぶんだ
Kaoru!
馨　馨　馨
Kaoru! Kaoru!
Hikaru- kun, you can't.
Get back in the game.
光君　君は駄目だ　試合に戻れ
Shut up!
黙れ
Hikaru...
光
Hikaru, take it easy.
光　落ち着くんだ
You can't go trying to feel my pain.
僕の痛みを感じ取っちゃいけない
Understand? You're not
the one who got hurt.
いいな　怪我してるのは　お前じゃない
It's no use. It hurts. It hurts, Kaoru!
無理だ
痛い　痛いよ　馨
Your pain is my pain. It doesn't matter
if no one else understands.
お前の痛みは僕の痛み
誰に理解されなくてもいい
As long as we're both there
for each other, we can go on living.
僕らはお互いさえいれば　生きていけるから
I envy you two.
君たちが　羨ましいな
Being able to support
each other like that...
そんなふうに支え合える相手がいて
Suou- senpai...
須王先輩
でも　須王先輩は学院のアイドルで
But Suou- senpai,
you're the academy's idol.
An idol, am I?
アイドル　か
If people are going to celebrate me
over a superficial title like that,
そんなうわべだけの呼び方でちやほやされるくらいなら
then I'm sure I'd be better off alone.
きっと　一人のほうがましだ
One injured heart
intersects with another.
傷ついた心と心が交差する すれ違い　傷つけあう
They pass each other,
and wound each other.
少年たちの心とは
What are the hearts
of these young men made of?
You can't run away any longer.
もう逃げられないよ
You're going to learn what happens
when you go against me.
僕に逆らうとどうなるかよく覚えておくんだね
Don't, Mitsukuni.
止せ　光邦
人を傷つける度　傷つき苦しむのは結局お前自身だ
Every time you hurt others,
you're the one who ends up being hurt.
僕に意見するな　崇
Don't try to give me any advice, Takashi.
You want me to put you
over my knee again?
またお仕置きされたいのか
Will it be the light of salvation
that ultimately awaits them?
やがて彼らを待つ結末とは　救いの光か　それとも
Or something else?
僕は身分不相応のやつが大嫌いなんだよ
I hate it when people try to rise
above their own station in life.
ハルちゃん　ごめんね　やっぱこんなのやだ
Haru-chan, I'm sorry!
I really can't do this!
Cut!!
カット　カット　カット　カット
Cut! Cut! Cut!
そこ　台本どおりにやれ
You there! Stick to the script!
But I...
だって
Cameraman, hold up for now!
カメラ　一旦止めて
Yes, boss.
イエス　ボース
Make the rain more heartrending!
雨もっと切なげに
Why have we suddenly gone from
talking about changing our characters
イエス　ボース
何でキャラ変更の話からいきなり映画撮影に
into a movie shoot?
それにしても　大げさな撮影隊ですね
And I have to say, it's an
overblown film crew, huh?
ハリウッドから急遽呼んだらしい
Apparently, she rushed them
here from Hollywood.
Haven't you ever seen them?
見たことないか
That man is the director of
"Millennial Snow," the vampire movie
あの人　昨年全米の興行成績第一位だったヴァンパイア映画
that was the number-one box-office hit
across America last year.
千年の雪の監督だ
くそ　金持ちめ
Damn these rich people...
And another thing, how come this script
has Kaoru being the pitcher?
大体この脚本　何で馨のほうが攻めになってるんだ
Yeah.
ね～
Pitcher?
攻めって
If you don't know, never mind.
分かんない子はいいの
Pitcher?
攻め
"Pitcher?"
Haruhi...
ハルヒ
How was my performance?
どうだった　俺の演技力は
It was awesome,
in one sense of the word,
ある意味すごかったです
at least insofar as how you're
able to be so enraptured by this.
何故そこまで陶酔できるかっという一点において
I've discovered a whole
new facet of myself.
俺は自分の新たな一面を発見したぞ
It's not that bad an idea to go
down this road for a little while.
しばらくはこの路線に行くのも悪くないな
そうですか
Are you sure?
Senpai, I think you're fine
just the way you are.
先輩は今のままでいいと思いますよ
そ　そうか
R-really?
Hmm, if you say so...
うん　お前がそう言うなら
影とか付くと　この人余計面倒そうだもんな
If this guy gets a darker side,
he'll just be that much more trouble.
ハルヒ君　出番ですわ
Haruhi- kun! You're on!
Okay!
こっちですわ
Over here!
I've just asked these two gentlemen
to make a special appearance.
今こちらの方々に特別出演お願いしていましたの
Appearance?
出演
What are you talking about?
何のことだ
クライマックスには　やはり悪役が必要ですわ
We're going to need some villains
for the big climax, after all.
The jumble of club members unite,
"At last, the time for the final
confrontation had arrived. There was
a greater evil infesting the academy"
バラバラだった部員たちが
真の悪者キャラと戦うことでひとつになる
to battle some true bad guy characters.
"Sons of the Japanese Mafia-
the brothers, Akutaro and Akujiro!!"
調書によると　この二人は資産家といっても
According to my notes, while these
two may be from a wealthy family,
実はジャパニーズマフィアのご子息
they are actually sons of members
of the Japanese Mafia.
These truly are ideal parts for you.
まさにうってつけな配役ですわ
What's with this girl?
何だこの女
Whatever my dad may be,
it's got nothing to do with me!
親が何だろうと俺には関係ねぇだろう
Hold on, Renge-chan...
ちょっと　蓮華ちゃん
- Okay, just stand by over here.
- Just a minute here...
さ　とにかくこちらでスタンバイを
ちょっと待って
好き放題言いやがって　図に乗ってんじゃねえ
You think you can push us around
however you want to? Come off it!
Look out!
危ない
痛っ
- Yow...
- Haruhi- kun! Are you okay!?
ハルヒ君　大丈夫？
その人たちの言うとおりだよ
Those boys are right.
Renge-chan, if you judge
people by stereotypes,
蓮華ちゃん　枠で人を図ってたら
you won't ever be able to see
what's really important.
本当に大切な物が何も見えなくなるよ
I'm not sure I understand
what you mean.
おっしゃる意味がよく分かりませんわ
ハルヒ　どうした
Haruhi! What happened!?
Which one of you started this?
手出したのはどっちだ
W-wait, Suou! She's the one
who started giving us a hard time!
ま　待って須王　先に絡んできたのはそっちだぜ
It's true, Senpai.
本当です　先輩
These boys aren't at fault.
この人たちは悪くない
- Run away!
逃げろ
Haruhi... does it hurt?
ハルヒ　痛むのか
Yes...
ええ　コンタクトが
It's my contact.
Huh? Your con... tact?
え　コン　タクト
ええ　ちょっとずれちゃって
Yeah. It slipped out.
Oh, so that's it!
そうか　そうか
Once you can cry without using eyedrops,
you're a full-fledged host!
目薬使わずに泣ければ　もう一人前のホストだ
カ　カ　カメラ　今の押さえまして！
Cameraman, did you catch that!?
Yes, boss!
イエス　ボス
Except for the contact falling out,
that was the ideal last scene!
コンタクトの落ち以外は　理想的なラストシーンですわ
All it needs now is for Kyoya-sama
to provide some moving narration.
あとは　鏡夜様に感動的なナレーションを
ノー　マイカメラが
No! My camera!
K-Kyoya-sama?
鏡　鏡夜様
I'm sorry, but I cannot
allow there to be any record
申し訳ないが
部員の暴力行為を記録に残すわけにはいかないんでね
of a club member engaging in violence.
I am extremely displeased at the way
you're acting like such a pest.
こういう迷惑のかけられかたは　非常に不愉快だ
何で
Why?
Kyoya-sama, you're supposed to
tell me not to worry about it,
鏡夜様なら「気にしなくていいよ」って
and then gently pat me on the head!
優しく頭を撫でてくれるはずなのに
Why would someone as kind
and affectionate as you...
慈愛に満ちた優しいあなたが　どうして
That's not who Kyoya is.
そんなの　鏡夜じゃないよ
It doesn't matter, does it?
いいんじゃない
Even if Kyoya- senpai is a little different
from what you expected, Renge-chan,
鏡夜先輩が蓮華ちゃんの思ってたような人とすこし違っても
I think that watching people,
ちゃんと人を見て　少しずつゆっくり知っていくのも
and slowly, little-by-little,
getting to know them,
楽しいと思うよ
can be fun, too.
Hey, Renge-chan, long time no see.
や　蓮華ちゃん　久しぶり
You look down, huh?
Come on, smile for me.
元気ないじゃん
ほら　笑いなよ　きょうはとてもいい日なんだから
Today is a very good day.
After all, Renge-chan,
you learned something
だって
蓮華ちゃんはこれから蓮華ちゃんが幸せに生きていくための
that's very important for you
to go on living a happy life.
とても大事なことを学んだんだ
You really have leveled up.
本当にレベルアップしたんだよ
"Several days later"
や　いらっしゃい
Hey there, come on in.
買いましたわ　例のビデオ
I bought that video!
Me too!
わたくしも
That scene in the rain
was the greatest!
あの雨のシーンが最高でしたわ
The lonesome prince!
孤独の王子様
The deep relationship
between Hikaru- sama
光様と馨様の深い関係が堪らなかったわ
and Kaoru- sama was too much!
ハニー君の鬼畜設定　もう一度見たい
I want to see Honey- kun
acting like a thug again!
あのハルヒ君の切ない表情
And Haruhi- kun's poignant expressions!
- Mori- kun was definitely
some kind of masochist, huh?
- Kyoya...
あのモリ君は絶対マゾ設定よね
鏡夜
I may have broken the lens,
レンズを壊したって
すでに撮影した映像は当然残ってるさ
but naturally, the footage that
was already shot still remains.
Of course, that one scene
of violence is cut out.
もちろん　例の暴力シーンはカットしてある
Sales have been pretty fair.
売上げはまあまあだな
That first-rate Hollywood staff
did as good a job as you'd expect.
さすがハリウッドの一流スタッフ　いい仕事を残してくれた
Is this what you meant by "interesting"?
おもしろいことってこれ
部費は多いに越したことはないだろう
It's best to have as much as we can
in the club budget, right?
At what point did this guy
start calculating all of this?
この人　一体どの辺から計算を
Take care.
ご機嫌よう
Huh? I thought you went home to France.
あれ　フランスに帰ったんじゃなかったのか
I realized something.
Your kindness earlier,
わたくし　気付いたんです
あの時身を挺して庇ってくれた優しさ
when you risked your life to protect me,
時に厳しく諭してくれた深い愛
and your deep love, for giving those,
at times, stern admonitions.
This is what you meant by watching people,
これが人をみて好きになるってことなのですわね　ハルヒ君
and falling in love with them,
right Haruhi- kun?
Yes?
Come, let's go to my house
to play some games together.
さあ　わたくしの家で一緒にゲームを致しましょう
You have to find out more about me, too.
わたくしのことも知っていただかなくては
Huh?
鏡夜先輩
Kyoya- senpai...
Are you sure this is okay?
いいの　あれ
Why wouldn't it be?
She's not wrong in what she's saying.
いいんじゃないか　言ってることは間違ってないし
No, it's not okay!
いや　よくない
They're both becoming friends with each
other as girls, just like you wanted.
お前のご希望通り　女の子同士の友達だぞ
あれは女の子同士じゃないだろう
But they're not both being girls!
さあ　ハルヒ君　参りましょう
Come on, Haruhi- kun! Let's go!
Wait! Don't take Haruhi away!
待って　ハルヒを連れていくな
You look ugly!
目つき悪いぞ
Your hairstyle is weird!
髪形が変だ
- Sex pixie!
- Sicko!
エロ河童
変態
How can this be? Hikaru and Kaoru...
なんてことだ　光と馨が
Next time, "The Twins Fight"
Ouran High School Host Club
will be waiting for you, next week!
桜蘭高校ホストクラブ　来週も
"Boom! Crash! Bang!"
お待ちしております